MICHAEL ROJAS

DESIGNER & DEVELOPER



PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Designer / Developer located in Virginia Beach with a Bs in Computer Science from ECPI University.

My passion is to create bold and captivating designs to help bring company's brands to life and solve problems. With a love for Digital Art, Photography, and Coding I have learned many related skills to help me knockout any project thrown at me. Whether it's User Research, Wireframing, Hi-Fidelity Mockups, T-shirt or Logo design or Coding different animations or full websites. I solve problems and enjoy making things look cool while doing it.

CONTACT



Address

4012 Barkleaf Dr, Virginia beach, VA 23462



Email

mrojasdev@gmail.com



Phone

757-305-7090

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, Javascript, CSS, SASS, LESS NPM, PHP, DNN, Wordpress, Bootstrap, Foundation, Git, Team Foundation Server

DESIGN SOFTWARE

Adobe CC, Figma, Sketch

DESIGN AWARDS

2018 Platinum AVA Digital Award
www.resiteonline.com

2018 Platinum AVA Digital Award www.livegrandmarc.com

EDUCATION

ECPI University - Jul 2011

B.S. Computer and Information Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER / CREATIVE DESIGNER

Resite Online - Virginia Beach, VA

August 2016 - Present

- UX Design Wireframes, Persona Research, Brand Research, High Fidelity Mocks
- · Talk clients during project overview, design calls, and revision phases
- Front End Development Code projects using HTML / CSS / JS /PHP and other front end tools
- · Accessibility Research
- · Graphic Design and Photography for internal marketing material

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGNER

Dominion Enterprises DX1 - Norfolk, VA

Oct 2013 - August 2016

- Conduct phone conversations with the dealer to discuss a client's business needs and the overall look of their website
- Design and develop responsive websites for several clients using DNN (DotNetNuke) and current web technologies (HTML,CSS,JS)
- Assist any teammates that have any questions about HTML, CSS, or javascript errors. Provide workflow suggestions to the team

CUSTOMER SERVICE - WEB BUILDER

Dominion Enterprises DX1 - Norfolk, VA

Jun 2012 - Oct 2013

- Migrate manage and maintain dealers content using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript
- Customer support duties included: Follow -ups with the dealer, over the phone trainings, email maintenance, professional meetings, and webinars